<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE posts SYSTEM 'posts.dtd'>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="3" CreationDate="2011-04-26T19:37:32.613" Score="53" ViewCount="77" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have some musical friends who might be interested in contributing to the private Beta?  Can I invite them or do they have to wait until the public Beta?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="51" LastEditorUserId="297" LastEditDate="2011-05-08T19:53:20.583" LastActivityDate="2011-05-08T19:53:20.583" Title="Can We Invite Anyone Else To The Private Beta?" Tags="&lt;support&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-04-26T19:39:21.567" Score="53" ViewCount="1336" Body="&lt;p&gt;I know on the Guitars site (soon to be merged with this one), &lt;a href=&quot;http://jtab.tardate.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JTab&lt;/a&gt; was used for rendering tablature notation (&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.guitars.stackexchange.com/questions/33/how-do-i-show-guitar-chord-and-tab-notation&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;see&lt;/a&gt;). For those not familiar with it, tab (&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tablature&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;tablature&lt;/a&gt;) is a simplifed music notation specifically for guitar playing. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Question 1: Will JTab be implemented here?&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://music.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/191/feature-request-jtab&quot;&gt;It has been&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Question 2: What other music notation will be implemented? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="51" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:48:05.437" LastActivityDate="2016-03-06T18:39:23.510" Title="Is there some sort of mark-up for music notation?" Tags="&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;music-notation&gt;" AnswerCount="7" CommentCount="8" FavoriteCount="19" ClosedDate="2016-04-02T20:36:41.623" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-04-26T19:41:00.753" Score="53" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't know of any way, unless they committed to the proposal in Area 51. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="51" LastActivityDate="2011-04-26T19:41:00.753" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-04-26T19:45:30.077" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;They will have to wait until the public beta. Which will be next week. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="47" LastActivityDate="2011-04-26T19:45:30.077" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-04-26T20:47:04.183" Score="7" ViewCount="125" Body="&lt;p&gt;Today, the topics include practice &amp;amp; performance, composition, technique, theory, and history. But not recording.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is no accident, from the discussions on Area51, recording is intentionally left out to not clash with audio.SE. However, audio.SE didn't take off. It is now likely that audio.SE will be &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.audio.stackexchange.com/questions/115/proposal-to-add-video-to-this-site&quot;&gt;expanded into a Audio and Video production&lt;/a&gt; site, moving it's scope even further away from recording music, which is a whole world away from making pod-casts and recording gunshots, which was two of the questions asked there before.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question is then, if whem the merge of Video into audio.SE happens, the questions related to recording music should be migrated here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="12" LastEditorUserId="12" LastEditDate="2011-04-27T14:22:49.247" LastActivityDate="2011-04-27T14:27:53.040" Title="Adding recording to the topics" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2011-04-26T21:00:23.773" Score="12" Body="&lt;h1&gt;No.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Audio Recording should not be merged with this site, or added to this site's scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, audio recording will be covered by the AV Production site.  If the AV site crashes and burns, that's a discussion for then and not now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, it would be bizarre and confusing for AVP to cover non-music audio and for us to cover recording music.  There's a huge overlap in the techniques, technology, etc. and there's no reason that people with expertise in recording audio shouldn't be able to talk about recording music.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While it's true that many musicians have recorded music and have expertise in that area, I would expect audio engineers who record music for a living to have greater expertise.  A much larger group with expertise in recording music should be present at the AVP site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And, while it's true that many musicians may have questions about recording their music, StackExchange makes it easy to direct them to the Audio site.  Moderators can also easily migrate questions to that site.  A large proportion of AVP users will be able to answer their questions, as opposed to the small proportion of musicians who have done serious audio production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also disagree with others who think music recording, or apects of it, should be on-topic on both sites.  That makes for confusion and a division of expertise.  There's also no clear line between the audio-engineer-technical-aspects and the musicality-aspects, and drawing one would be likely to alienate people. Technicians wouldn't react well to being told they aren't &quot;musical enough&quot;, and that sort of thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28" LastEditorUserId="28" LastEditDate="2011-04-27T14:27:53.040" LastActivityDate="2011-04-27T14:27:53.040" CommentCount="19" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-04-26T22:44:49.020" Score="6" ViewCount="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;I joined this SE because I see the death of guitars.SE as practically inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Will there be some form of reputation migration from other sites as they are folded into this one?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastEditorUserId="297" LastEditDate="2011-05-08T19:52:29.770" LastActivityDate="2011-05-08T19:52:29.770" Title="Reputation migration?" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;migration&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2011-04-26T22:52:26.710" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes.  If your account here and your account there are linked, your questions and answers will belong to you if a question is migrated (along with the rep you got/lost from them).  When Guitars is closed, the StackExchange people will do their best to ensure all the questions moved here get assigned to the right accounts.  Again, this should be no problem if your accounts are linked.  Otherwise, just speak up before it happens (there should be an announcement) and they can get things resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If something gets messed up, just flag the question or answer and ask a moderator to fix it (if they can't, they can contact the overlords).  It's much preferred that you have everything straightened out beforehand, though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's a post on meta.guitars that talks about the upcoming merge and what will happen: &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.guitars.stackexchange.com/questions/136/announcement-save-guitars-se-by-supporting-the-music-proposal&quot;&gt;http://meta.guitars.stackexchange.com/questions/136/announcement-save-guitars-se-by-supporting-the-music-proposal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28" LastEditorUserId="28" LastEditDate="2011-04-26T23:48:48.350" LastActivityDate="2011-04-26T23:48:48.350" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-04-27T00:46:56.223" Score="10" ViewCount="193" Body="&lt;p&gt;I wanted to ask a question about bass guitar, and I realized that since this is now a universal music site, that I can't just use &quot;bass&quot; as a tag like I could on the Guitars.SE due to potential confusion with the double-bass. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I want to tag a question for bass guitar, should I use &quot;bass guitar&quot; or &quot;bass&quot; and &quot;guitar&quot;? For the former case, I can see it being more useful for keeping the tag list succinct and being easier to favorite/ignore. For the latter case, some questions about bass sound/technique may be applicable to both bass guitar and double-bass. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If one was playing an acoustic bass guitar, should one then use &quot;acoustic bass guitar,&quot; &quot;acoustic&quot; and &quot;bass guitar&quot; as two tags, or &quot;acoustic,&quot; &quot;bass,&quot; and &quot;guitar&quot; as three separate tags?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see, this can get all kinds of confusing, and I'm wondering if there is a standard that the community has agreed upon, and if so, what is it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="64" LastEditorUserId="48" LastEditDate="2011-05-10T07:25:16.447" LastActivityDate="2014-02-18T17:53:10.607" Title="Instrument tagging standards" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
</posts>